To a world of dreams...
with the one you love.
Today's our first date in a
long time, and it's special.
To a world of dreams
with the one
Because today, I get to be with
Shikimori-san until late tonight!
I came up with a plan to make
sure she'll have a good time.
I'm gonna make sure this goes perfectly!
Izumi-san!
Did I keep you waiting?
Y-Your outfit...
Oh, I thought a skirt might
be too restrictive.
I wanted something comfortable
to walk around in,
so I borrowed my mom's coat.
She...
She looks so cool!
Are you listening?
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#12  Better Than a Dream
Wh-Where should we start?
Heh, heh, heh.
First order of business is...
This, of course!
E-Ears? They're cute!
B-But that kind of thing
isn't really for me.
Embarrassed to Death
I'd like to see you in some, though...
I'd love to see you wear them.
Um... well, then...
I'll take this!
A s-skull?!
But look. If I fasten up my coat...
Doesn't it sort of match what I'm wearing?
She's a prince from the underworld!
A million points!
Yay!
Let's ride this first.
Okay.
There's a 90-minute wait?!
Well, it just opened last year.
If you don't get here early,
apparently it can take up to 180 minutes.
W-Wow...
Look at this!
Briars, huh?
Briar Rose... She's from
Sleeping Beauty, right?
What was that story about again?
The princess is cursed
to slumber for a hundred years.
And in that time, the castle
becomes overgrown with briars.
The prince braves the thicket,
heedless of the danger,
to find the princess. He then kisses her,
freeing her from her century-long curse.
I had no idea. So that's how it goes...
Yeah, you don't seem
like you'd be into fairy tales.
How rude! I liked picture books
just like everyone else!
But you didn't know Sleeping Beauty?
Which was your favorite, then?
Um, uh...
The Ugly Duckling, maybe?
That's so dark! Did something
sad happen to you?
No, of course not!
I just enjoy things that have a little edge,
like horror and suspense.
Still dark.
And that's still rude!
Remember the first time we went
to see a movie together
and you said you were okay
with whatever I wanted to see?
Yes.
Then at the fireworks, you said
you wanted me to see your cute side.
But I want to see all of you,
not just your cute side.
Of course, I already know your
proud side that hates to lose.
Hey, Shikimori-san, do you have a dream?
I do, actually.
Really? What is it?
I once read a shojo manga...
A romance story.
It made me think love was amazing.
My dream is to experience it for myself.
Love?
But that dream's already come true.
Still waiting...
This is taking ages.
Step forward, please.
That 90-minute wait kinda
flew right by, huh?
It sure did.
Be careful. Watch yourself.
Here we go.
This is so exciting!
Right?
Welcome to the world of Sleeping Beauty.
It's a slower ride than I thought.
There are some aromatic fragrances,
pretty music, and a gentle rocking...
I-I'm getting sleeping...
Isn't it lovely, Izumi-san?
Izumi-san?
After being kissed by the prince,
Sleeping Beauty awoke from
her hundred-year slumber.
Welcome back!
The ride's over, Izumi-san!
I fell asleep toward the end...
But it was really pretty, wasn't it?
I-It really was.
I can still smell that nice aroma.
What did you think? Did you enjoy it?
Of course!
Although I wasn't expecting such a long wait.
Yeah. Shall we go for one
with a shorter line next?
Shikimori-san?
I'd wait in any line.
Sh-Shikimori?
Because as long as I'm with you,
any time we spend together
is just so much fun!
I agree!
Okay, let's get to the next one!
We gotta hurry before it gets dark!
There's no need to rush.
We have plenty of time.
What?!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
We gave your table to
another guest by mistake,
and all the tables for the course
you reserved are already taken.
O-Of all the luck!
This was the centerpiece
of my entire date plan!
I could arrange a different table.
Oh... Really? That'd be great.
This is...
This is an incredible upgrade!
What would you like to drink?
O-Orange juice, please.
I'll have a ginger ale.
Certainly.
Th-The lady up front was really nice, huh?
Yes, to give us such an expensive table...
It's way too formal!
My jacket sticks out like a sore thumb!
Here you are, sir.
Thanks!
You switched gears fast!
Wow, this looks so good!
Wait, is this napkin supposed
to go over my lap?
I think so, yes.
Why are there so many forks?
I've heard you start with
the one on the outside.
Yum!
Izumi-san...
Your eyes are always
glimmering like a child's.
Aw, I made you self-conscious.
Did I get carried away?
Don't worry yourself.
When I'm with you, Izumi-san,
all kinds of things seem
prettier than usual to me.
So I have to wonder sometimes...
How beautiful must the world
look through your eyes?
You know?
Y-You're exaggerating.
Wh-What do I do?
I can't even tell how
the food tastes anymore!
Hey, Izumi-san...
What do you see in my eyes?
Well, uh...
M-Me?
That's right.
You're all I'm ever looking at, Izumi-san.
She's just not letting up with the overkill!
Well, for me, too...
The most b-beautiful thing I see... is you.
Uh...
I'll take any dishes you're finished with.
Okay!
Whew, I'm stuffed.
Full-course meals really are a lot of food.
We still have some time.
Is there anywhere you want to go?
Shikimori-san?
I want...
t-to do what they did in the commercial!
Okay, sure.
Huh?!
To a world of dreams
with the one you love
A-Are you sure about this?
Y-You agreed so readily...
Yeah. Let's not waste any time.
Right here?!
Your hand.
Hohay...
So... how do I escort you, exactly?
Huh?
Huh? Well, when you said
"what they did in the commercial,"
you meant after the little girl's
parents take her hands, didn't you?
Yes...
So the part where the old man
escorts the old lady, right?
Wait, that's not what you meant?!
Sorry! Um, then which part did you mean?
This is fun in its own way, so it's fine...
Let's go somewhere we can just talk awhile.
O-Okay. Let's find a place with
a nice view of the sunset.
Be sure to escort me properly, my prince.
R-Right!
Let's go.
What was it she really wanted to do, though?
At the end of that commercial, I think...
Sh-She couldn't have meant...
Off you go!
This view is really great.
It's beautiful.
Y-Yeah, it is.
What now?
Since I figured out what she meant about
the commercial, I'm all nervous...
Oh, I know! We haven't taken a picture
yet today. Let's get one!
Good idea.
Here we go.
Is the background in it?
Okay, say cheese—
Huh?!
Wait, why...
Attention, guests.
The park is currently
experiencing a power outage.
Please bear with us until power is restored.
There goes my bad luck!
And our gorgeous nighttime scenery!
The boat stopped, too...
Are you okay, Shikimori-san?
I'm just fine.
Here.
Thanks.
The other boats have lights.
We can use our smartphones, too.
Good idea.
Wow...
It really is pitch black.
I can't see anything but the moon.
I'm sorry. I never dreamed this would happen.
I hope they get the power back on soon.
But...
Wha—
Now it really is just the two of us.
See?! This is what I'm talking about!
You're just like a prince!
How can you do that so naturally?!
Does it make you happy?
Incredibly!
I'm glad, then.
It's kind of weird, isn't it?
I can't see anything but you here.
Yeah...
It's like being in a dream.
For just this moment, there's nothing
else to steal your attention,
so you're looking only at me.
If I could have dreams like this,
I wouldn't want to wake up.
What if you end up drifting
far away from me?
What can I do...
to make you feel at ease?
Careful—
I love you.
I'm in love with you, Shikimori-san.
I'll stay with you forever.
So please don't worry anymore.
I'm really...
no match for you.
Shikimori-san, the lights are back.
Let me stay like this a bit longer.
I guess she doesn't want to wake up
from the dream just yet.
Sh-Shikimori-san...
Also, I didn't mean for what
I said to turn that serious.
Huh? Y-You didn't?
But right now...
I'm happier than I'd be in any dream.
Good.
Hey, Izumi...
Why do you look like some
modern art installment?
I didn't think about it until I was
in the bath after I got home last night...
Hey, you listening?
But...
How could I have done
something so assertive?!
You can twist yourself up even more?!
Come on, tell us!
We know something happened, Micchon!
You're better off just spilling now.
R-R-Really, nothing happened at all.
Yeah, you're a lousy liar.
She's not talking, Inspector.
Clearly, there's been some
sort of development.
Hmm... Silence in this case
can only mean one thing.
You kissed, didn't you?
What?!
You k-k-k-kissed him?!
For real?!
Not so loud!
Er... Oh?
W-Would you mind explaining
in a bit more detail?
Relax, Assistant Inspector.
We had dinner at a really
upscale restaurant,
so the mood was right.
Then we took a gondola ride...
Uh-huh...
But the power went out.
Everything went dark.
His bad luck never fails.
And that's when Izumi-san...
k-kissed my cheek.
We're done here.
That stupid Izumi wimped out.
N-No, he didn't!
He, well... seemed to think
I was feeling uneasy,
so he did it to comfort me.
He was very sweet.
I see.
And also...
Uh-huh?
I've been wanting to get as close
as possible to Izumi-san lately,
so I was being pretty proactive, but...
Wait, wait! Don't suddenly go all carnivore!
The warm and fuzzies just
instantly burned to ash.
I was panicking because
I made him worry about me.
I was ashamed of myself for getting
distracted by a bunch of superficial stuff.
Micchon, hang on a—
So I've made up my mind.
I'm going to become
as open-hearted as Izumi-san.
R-Really? Well, your love is
plenty big enough already...
So are your fluctuations.
What do you think, Hachimitsu?
I can't tell if they're kindergarteners
or an elderly couple.
Just hang on. I'll get out of that knot.
But hey, as long as they're happy,
it's all good.
SEE YOU~
Shikimori-san!
Good morning, Shikimori-san.
Good morning, Izumi-san.
My girlfriend is super cute, and also...
incredibly cool.
Shall we?
That was amazing, Shikimori-san!
You got it in one shot!
Just incredible! You're so cool!
I think that's enough, Izumi-san...
Come on, let's go.